The CUE event is an event that's held every year at Bodwell
CUE 행사는 보드웰에서 매년 실시하는 행사로
where 50 Canadian universities come to Bodwell to speak to our students
50개의 캐나다 대학들이 보드웰로 찾아와서 학생과 만나는 시간입니다
They have the opportunities to speak directly to admission reps from various universities
학생은 다양한 대학의 입학 담당자들과 직접 얘기해 볼 수 있는 기회를 갖고
ask them questions about admission
입학 및 요건에 대해 물어볼 수 있습니다
and admission requirements. We actually encourage grades 10 11 and 12 students to attend
학교에서는 10, 11, 12학년 학생들이 행사에 참가하도록 권장하고 있습니다
They can ask any question regarding
학생은 입학 요건에 관련하여
admission requirements everything from averages needed
평균 학점, 들어야 하는 과목, 추가 서류, 기타 기준 등
Courses that universities are looking for, supplementary applications, and other criterias that universities might be looking for
대학에서 요구하는 모든 것에 대해 질문할 수 있습니다
Since not all university requirements are the same
모든 대학의 입학 요건이 같지 않기 때문에
it's imperative for students to talk to the admission officers
학생이 다양한 대학 입학 담당자들에게
from various universities to ask them specific questions about their admission criteria and requirements
입학 기준과 요건에 대하여 자세히 물어보는 것이 중요합니다
Bodwell hosts the CUE event to give our students opportunity to speak to those university reps in person
보드웰의 CUE 행사는 학생들이 그런 대학 담당자들과 직접 얘기해볼 수 있는 자리입니다
The next step for our students is to do a follow up with their counselors by sitting down with them
그 후에 학생은 카운셀러와 함께 대학에 대해 추가적으로 알아볼 수 있습니다
They sit down with the counselors one-on-one after the event to discuss the various options
학생은 행사가 끝나고 카운셀러와 일대일로 앉아서 다양한 옵션과
and opportunities they have learned themselves at the CUE event
CUE 행사에서 알게된 여러가지 기회에 대해 상의합니다
Rather than having our students miss school to go meet
학생이 50개의 대학에
50 universities at 50 different locations
시간내서 일일이 찾아가는 것보다
It's an opportunity for our students to have all 50 reps in one place and talk to them in person
50명의 담당자들과 한 곳에서 얘기해볼 수 있다는 것은 좋은 기회입니다
They can also make personal connection with the University reps
또한 학생은 대학 담당자와 개별적으로 연락할 수도 있습니다
They will have their contact information and they will be able to contact them one-on-one in case they needed to
필요시에는 행사에서 받은 연락처로 연락해서 일대일로 문의할 수 있습니다
Prior to attending this event
행사 전 학생은
students are encouraged in class,
수업시간 또는 카운셀러와 함께
and through meeting with counsellors to ask specific questions to the University reps
대학 담당자들과 만나게 되면 어떤 질문을 할지 준비합니다
Those questions are discussed in CLE  classes and when the students meet with their counsellors back again 1 on 1
이런 질문은 CLE 수업 및 카운셀러와 일대일로 만날때 상의됩니다